# CHRIS AFAYOMIDE

# Fullstack Developer

+234-8142360551 | daraseyi086@gmail.com | <u>https://seyi.vercel.app</u>

# **PROFILE**

Fullstack developer with over 4 years experience.

I have successfully launched learning platforms, e-commerce sites, and blockchain projects I have worked as an intern, backend developer, frontend developer and as a fullstack developer for various organizations.

I love listening to music, working out, watching sitcoms, and most importantly, writing code.
I enjoy solving problems and applying logic with creativity.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

# **Plusworld Roofing**

February 2024 - Present

- I am building the web app for the Plusworld Academy learning platform to teach construction courses.
- Optimized performance and deployment using AWS, ensuring 99.9% uptime
- You can view the deployed version here at <a href="https://plusworld.vercel.app">https://plusworld.vercel.app</a>
- · I used typescript, next.js for the frontend
- I use postgres nodejs, aws for the backend and to store data.
- I helped to test and build the dandys beauty app, a child company of plusworld. available on playstore and apple store
- I started as an intern and was later made a permanent staff after three months for my unmatched work ethic

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER (PROJECT)

#### **Afro Royals**

November 2023 - July 2024 (Project)

- I independently developed and designed from scratch a fully customizable web app to sell african fabrics
- I integrated a apayment system with the paystack api
- You can view the deployed version at <a href="https://afrifashion.vercel.app">https://afrifashion.vercel.app</a>
- You can view the github repo at <a href="https://github.com/afayomide/afrifashion">https://github.com/afayomide/afrifashion</a>
- I worked on both the frontend and backend.
- I used javascript, react for the frontend
- I used mongo, nodejs, google cloud platform for the backend and to store data.

#### FULLSTACK DEVELOPER (PERSONAL PROJECT)

# **Audet Blog**

August 2024 - Present (Personal Project)

- I independently developed and designed a fully customizable web app to upload and read music blogs
- You can view it here at <a href="https://audet.vercel.app">https://audet.vercel.app</a>
- You can view the github repo at <a href="https://github.com/afayomide/audet">https://github.com/afayomide/audet</a>
- I worked on both the frontend and backend.
- I used typescript, nextis for the frontend
- I used postgres, nodejs, google cloud, for the backend and to store data.

#### FULLSTACK DEVELOPER (PERSONAL PROJECT)

#### AdotAdvisor

september 2023 - October 2023

- I Independently developed and designed from scratch a fully customizable web app to give information on the stock market
- You can view it here at <a href="https://adotadvisor.vercel.app">https://adotadvisor.vercel.app</a>
- You can view the github repo at <a href="https://github.com/afayomide/adotadvisor">https://github.com/afayomide/adotadvisor</a>
- I worked on both the frontend and backend.
- I also built the mobile app version
- You can view the github repo at <a href="https://github.com/afayomide/adotadvisorapp">https://github.com/afayomide/adotadvisorapp</a>
- I used javascript, React for the frontend
- I used mongo, nodejs, for the backend and to store data.

#### FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

### alphasniffer

hune 2023 - August 2023

- I singlehandedly built and designed from scratch a fully customizable web app for the launch of a crypto project, alphasniffer
- I worked on both the frontend and backend.
- I used javascript, React for the frontend

#### OTHER OLDER PROJECTS

scentsbyfolak : https://scentsbyfolak.vercel.app/

Mksignature : <a href="https://mksignature-afayomide.vercel.app/">https://mksignature-afayomide.vercel.app/</a>

Youtubemusic : <a href="https://youtubemusic-nu.vercel.app">https://youtubemusic-nu.vercel.app</a>

# **EDUCATION**

#### Course

2024

Harvard Computer Science - CS50

#### Course

2021

Udemy - Fullstack Development course <a href="https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-ae070ffc-8e29-4436-b853-409ad816eeb1/">https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-ae070ffc-8e29-4436-b853-409ad816eeb1/</a>

#### Course

2024

Univeristy at buffalo - Blockchain/Dapps <a href="https://coursera.org/verify/UGOZG8RNAAB9">https://coursera.org/verify/UGOZG8RNAAB9</a>

#### Course

2022

META|FACEBOOK - Frontend Developer https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/certificate/8C8DHXPZX4AD

# University

2023

Ekiti state University - Physiology

# **SKILLS**

- Javascript
- Typescript
- Nextjs
- React && React Native
- vueis
- node.js Express && Nestjs
- postgreSQL
- mongo
- bootstrap
- aws (cloud storage)
- tailwind
- · VPS expert, email administrator
- Git && Github

# REFERENCE

Project Manager && SCRUM MASTER - Plusworld Academy

nAOMI ANEZU

+234 907 208 7522 - naomianezu@gmail.com